{
    "subject": "resource/Michael_Stoute",
    "predicate": "ontology/raceHorse",
    "object": "resource/Green_Desert_(horse)",
    "human_readable": "Michael Stoute has a race horse named Green Desert.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.923428475856781,
            "question": "Is Green Desert owned by Michael Stoute?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8669930696487427,
            "question": "Does Green Desert compete in horse racing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8630880117416382,
            "question": "What is the name of Michael Stoute's race horse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8563941121101379,
            "question": "Who owns the race horse Green Desert?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7817341685295105,
            "question": "What is the name of the race horse owned by Michael Stoute?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7785780429840088,
            "question": "Does Michael Stoute own a race horse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6035739779472351,
            "question": "What kind of animal is Green Desert?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5483611226081848,
            "question": "Who breeds Green Desert?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4352419674396515,
            "question": "Is Michael Stoute a famous horse trainer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23225535452365875,
            "question": "What does Michael Stoute do for a living?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Michael Stoute has a race horse named Green Desert.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4277_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Michael Stoute a famous horse trainer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4277_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who breeds Green Desert?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4277_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of animal is Green Desert?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4277_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4277_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4277_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4277_150.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4277_152.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4277_155.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4277_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4277_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4277_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4277_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4277_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The first document mentions \"Green Desert\" as a racehorse, and the subsequent documents discuss Sir Michael Stoute's career as a horse racing trainer, mentioning Green Desert as one of his horses."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents contain information about Sir Michael Stoute and his achievements in horse racing, including the details about the racehorse Green Desert. Specifically, it states that \u201cGreen Desert was a horse I loved training; he had a huge amount of vitality and personality,\u201d said Stoute. This supports the statement that Michael Stoute has a racehorse named Green Desert."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}